Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Master Tapes Series (MT), 1993-1997 [RESTRICTED], 14 boxes
  - Norfolk, Va. and Environs
    - Goss, Jocelyn (Box MT10)
    - Gowens, Madeline (Box MT10)
    - Gray, Cecille (Box MT10)
    - Grimstead, Lucille (Box MT10)
    - Grimstead, Sarah (Box MT10)
    - Hall, Doris (Box MT10)
    - Hayslette, Elnora (Box MT10)
    - Johnson, Harvey (Box MT10)
    - Johnson, Jessie (Box MT10)
    - Lawson, Arthur (Box MT10)
    - Lawson, Leon (Box MT10)
    - Linyear, Josephine (Box MT10)
    - Linyear, William (Box MT10)
    - Littlejohn, Toledo (Box MT10)
    - Lloyd, Esther (Box MT10)
    - Mitchell, Alma (Box MT10)
    - Morgan, Donald (Box MT10)
    - Neal, Andrew (Box MT10)
    - Neal, Velma (Box MT10)
    - Owens, Catherine (Box MT10)
    - Owens, Eugene (Box MT10)
    - Parrish, Doris (Box MT10)
    - Peevy, Evelyn (Box MT10)
    - Perry, Jean (Box MT10)
    - Pharr, Naomi (Box MT10)
    - Phillips, Hazel (Box MT10)
    - Phillips, Jesse (Box MT10)
    - Phillips, Jesse (Box MT10)
    - Porter, Celestine (Box MT10)
    - Rattley, Jessie (Box MT10)
    - Riddick, Mozelle (Box MT10)
    - Riddick, Paul (Box MT10)
    - Rodgers, Alberta (Box MT10)
    - Ryder, Georgia (Box MT10)
    - Sharp, Clarice (Box MT10)
    - Skyles, Walter (Box MT11)
    - Stith, Leah (Box MT11)
    - Studivant, Lenora (Box MT11)
    - Wallace, Jeanette (Box MT11)
    - Watson, William (Box MT11)
    - Wells, Cassie (Box MT11)
    - White, Addie (Box MT11)
    - White, Patricia (Box MT11)
    - Williams, Elwood (Box MT11)
    - Williams, Hortense (Box MT11)
    - Wyatt, George (Box MT11)
  - Orangeburg, S.C. and Environs
    - Adams, Benjamin (Box MT11)
    - Adams, Fannie (Box MT11)
    - Bonds, Solomon, Jr. (Box MT11)
    - Briggman, Theodue (Box MT11)
    - Brooks, Charles, Sr. (Box MT11)
    - Brunson, John (Box MT11)
    - Caldwell, Rossie (Box MT11)
    - Dawson, Gracia (Box MT11)
    - Felder, Julius (Box MT11)
    - Finney, Ernest, Jr. (Box MT11)
    - Georgia, Mr. (Box MT11)
    - Gilbert, Amy (Box MT11)
    - Gore, Blinzy (Box MT11)
    - Harp, Matie (Box MT11)
    - Harper, II, John (Box MT11)
    - Hassell, Betty (Box MT11)
    - Henderson, Ernest (Box MT11)
    - Henderson, Ophelia (Box MT11)
    - Hubbard, Robert (Box MT11)
    - Jamison, Annie (Box MT11)
    - Jamison, Marion, Jr. (Box MT11)
    - Jenkins, Barbara (Box MT11)
    - Kerford, Leo (Box MT11)
    - Lewis, Mary (Box MT11)
    - Lott, Sudie (Box MT11)
    - Martin, Hattie (Box MT11)
    - Martin, II, Frank (Box MT11)
    - Mathews, Sarah (Box MT11)
    - McCollom, Irene (Box MT11)
    - McCollom, James (Box MT11)
    - Middleton, Bernice (Box MT11)
    - Middleton, Earl (Box MT11)
    - Mitchell, L. (Box MT11)
    - Mitchell, Rachel (Box MT11)
    - Montgomery, Eugene (Box MT11)
    - Pendergrass, Norman, Sr. (Box MT11)
    - Poole, Larence (Box MT11)
    - Reagan, Mrs. (Box MT11)
    - Richburg, Joseph (Box MT11)
    - Roland, Harold (Box MT11)
    - Sharrow, Marion (Box MT11)
    - Smith, Haulean (Box MT11)
    - Smith, Mr. (Box MT11)
    - Sulton, James, Jr. (Box MT11)
    - Thompson, Nettie (Box MT11)
    - Townsend, Zack (Box MT11)
    - Twiggs, Leo (Box MT11)
    - Walker, Cloria (Box MT11)
    - Washington, Camilla (Box MT11)
    - Weise, Aunt (Box MT11)
    - Williams, Ethel (Box MT11)
    - Wright, Minnie (Box MT11)
    - Zimmerman, Geraldyne (Box MT11)
  - St. Helena, S.C. and Environs
    - Atkins, Earnestine (Box MT11)
    - Barnwell, Rosalie (Box MT11)
    - Beasley, Jonathon (Box MT11)
    - Brown, George (Box MT11)
    - Brown, Leroy (Box MT11)
    - Browne, Corinne (Box MT11)
    - Bryan, Helen (Box MT11)
    - Bryant, Eddie (Box MT11)
    - Bundick, Elizabeth (Box MT11)
    - Carr, Peter (Box MT11)
    - Carr, Rebecca (Box MT11)
    - Chaplin, Eva (Box MT11)
    - Daise, Kathleen (Box MT11)
    - Frazier, Coazell (Box MT11)
    - Gaston, Irene (Box MT11)
    - Henderson, David (Box MT11)
    - Holmes, Ercell (Box MT11)
    - Holmes, Laura (Box MT11)
    - Holmes, Lula (Box MT11)
    - Holmes, William (Box MT11)
    - Jones, Emma (Box MT11)
    - Legree, Joseph (Box MT11)
    - Major, Evangeline (Box MT11)
    - Mann, Etta (Box MT11)
    - Middleton, Richard (Box MT11)
    - Nesbit, Louise (Box MT11)
    - Orr, Isaiah (Box MT11)
    - Patterson, Alexandria (Box MT11)
    - Singleton, D. (Box MT11)
    - Singleton, Kato (Box MT11)
    - Small, Henry (Box MT12)
    - Weathers, George (Box MT12)
    - Willborn, Isaac (Box MT12)
    - Williams, Jonathan (Box MT12)
    - Wright, Robbie (Box MT12)
  - Summerton, S.C. and Environs
    - Allen, Ida (Box MT12)
    - Allen, Johnny (Box MT12)
    - Anderson, Willie Mae (Box MT12)
    - Bethune, Thelmer (Box MT12)
    - Briggs, Eliza (Box MT12)
    - Briggs, Willie Mae (Box MT12)
    - Butler, B. (Box MT12)
    - Canty, John (Box MT12)
    - Canty, Mary (Box MT12)
    - Carter, Mamie (Box MT12)
    - Chandler, Janette (Box MT12)
    - DeLaine, Marguirite (Box MT12)
    - Doctor-Wearing, Alice (Box MT12)
    - Dow, Willine (Box MT12)
    - Fleming, Abraham (Box MT12)
    - Flood, John (Box MT12)
    - Frierson, Carnetta (Box MT12)
    - Frierson, Mary (Box MT12)
    - Georgia, Robert (Box MT12)
    - Gordon, Sammy, Jr. (Box MT12)
    - Gray, Ruben (Box MT12)
    - Green, Melison (Box MT12)
    - Gregory, Celestine (Box MT12)
    - Howard, Sallie (Box MT12)
    - Kennedy, Chars (Box MT12)
    - Leneau, Octavia (Box MT12)
    - Levy, Moses (Box MT12)
    - McCray, Josephine (Box MT12)
    - Nelson, Margaret (Box MT12)
    - Parks, Leola (Box MT12)
    - Pearson, Ferdinand (Box MT12)
    - Poole, Lorene (Box MT12)
    - Ragin, General (Box MT12)
    - Richardson, Ruth (Box MT12)
    - Richburg, Joseph (Box MT12)
    - Smith, Abraham (Box MT12)
    - Smith, Elease (Box MT12)
    - Smith, Elease (Box MT12)
    - Smith, Haulean (Box MT12)
    - Walters, Katie (Box MT12)
    - Washington, Sallie (Box MT12)
    - Wells, Julia (Box MT12)
    - Williams, Cornelias (Box MT12)
    - Wright, Minnie (Box MT12)
    - Young, Samuel (Box MT12)
  - Tallahassee, Fla. and Environs
    - Anderson, Dora (Box MT12)
    - andrews, Malachia (Box MT12)
    - Boardly, Barbara (Box MT12)
    - Campbell, Witt (Box MT12)
    - Carr, Carrie (Box MT12)
    - Clausell, Bernyce (Box MT12)
    - Davis, Peggy (Box MT12)
    - Diallo, Mary (Box MT12)
    - Dixie, A. (Box MT12)
    - Dixie, Laura (Box MT12)
    - Dixie, Samuel (Box MT12)
    - Eaton, James (Box MT12)
    - Farmer, Martha (Box MT12)
    - Gaines, Mary (Box MT12)
    - Griffin, Robert (Box MT12)
    - Hackley, Sallie (Box MT12)
    - Harris, Bessie (Box MT12)
    - Hogans, Angelina (Box MT12)
    - Howell, Aquilina (Box MT12)
    - Huntley, John (Box MT12)
    - Jefferson, Harrieta (Box MT12)
    - Jones, Dorothy (Box MT12)
    - Kelly, Vivian (Box MT12)
    - Kemp, Ethel (Box MT12)
    - King, Gertrude (Box MT12)
    - Lewis, Clarence (Box MT12)
    - Matheus, Ellen (Box MT12)
    - McClendon, Mavis (Box MT12)
    - Miller, Gertrude (Box MT12)
    - Mungen, Robert (Box MT12)
    - Nims, H. (Box MT12)
    - Palmer, James (Box MT12)
    - Parker, Florida (Box MT12)
    - Peacock, Alice (Box MT12)
    - Perry, Benjamin (Box MT12)
    - PinochleClub (Box MT12)
    - Robinson, Lillie (Box MT12)
    - Russell, Sue (Box MT12)
    - Sanford, Lessie (Box MT12)
    - Simmons, Sarah (Box MT12)
    - Smith, Charles (Box MT12)
    - Speed, Cornelius (Box MT12)
    - Stephens, Edwina (Box MT12)
    - Thorpe, Annette (Box MT12)
    - Thorpe, Edwin (Box MT12)
    - Walker, Courtney (Box MT12)
    - Washington, Samuel, Jr. (Box MT12)
    - Williams, Gertrude (Box MT12)
    - Williams, Myrtle (Box MT12)
    - Wilson, Roosevelt (Box MT12)
    - Young, Daisey (Box MT12)
  - Tuskegee, Ala. and Environs
    - Baldwin, Wilhelmina (Box MT12)
    - Baldwin, Wilhelmina (Box MT13)
    - Beasley, David (Box MT13)
    - Bentley, Frank (Box MT13)
    - Brown, Cordelia (Box MT13)
    - Cooley, Fannie (Box MT13)
    - Donald, Edward (Box MT13)
    - Ducksworth, Lee (Box MT13)
    - Ferrell, George (Box MT13)
    - Ford, Johnny (Box MT13)
    - Graham, Mai (Box MT13)
    - Grant, Ernest (Box MT13)
    - Green, Elbert (Box MT13)
    - Hall, Annie (Box MT13)
    - Hall, Ezell (Box MT13)
    - Hooten, Henry (Box MT13)
    - Hooten, Lillian (Box MT13)
    - Jones, Ira (Box MT13)
    - Jones, Wilhelmina (Box MT13)
    - Judkins, Marian (Box MT13)
    - Judkins, Robert (Box MT13)
    - Lee, Detroit (Box MT13)
    - Lyles, Demetrice (Box MT13)
    - Marable, Clarence (Box MT13)
    - Mayberry, Bennie (Box MT13)
    - McCorvey, Sandy (Box MT13)
    - Owens, Johnnie (Box MT13)
    - Paris, George (Box MT13)
    - Pinkard, Otis (Box MT13)
    - Pointer, Ann (Box MT13)
    - Pollard, Charles (Box MT13)
    - Poole, Georgia (Box MT13)
    - Price, John (Box MT13)
    - Quinn, Bettie (Box MT13)
    - Quinn, Hersey (Box MT13)
    - Randolph, L. (Box MT13)
    - Robinson, Amelia (Box MT13)
    - Sullins, Della (Box MT13)
    - Taylor, William (Box MT13)
    - Thomas, Elaine (Box MT13)
    - Toland, Frank (Box MT13)
    - Walker, Archie (Box MT13)
    - Walker, Claudius (Box MT13)
    - Walker, Ferdie (Box MT13)
    - Wallace, Alfreda (Box MT13)
    - Wells, Ida (Box MT13)
    - Whitehead, Willie (Box MT13)
    - Woodson, James (Box MT13)
    - Wright, Jessie (Box MT13)
    - Young, Kenneth (Box MT13)
  - Wilmington, N.C. and Environs
    - Alexander, Camille (Box MT13)
    - Baker, George (Box MT13)
    - Berry, Lisbon (Box MT13)
    - Berry, Shirley (Box MT13)
    - Boykin, Hartford (Box MT13)
    - Bryant, Charles (Box MT13)
    - Burnett, Elijah (Box MT13)
    - Chestnut, Carter (Box MT13)
    - Childs, William (Box MT13)
    - Coco, Joan (Box MT13)
    - Cooper, Ida (Box MT13)
    - Davis, George (Box MT13)
    - Davis, Ruth (Box MT13)
    - Donaldson, Henry (Box MT13)
    - Donaldson, Laura (Box MT13)
    - Epps, Doris (Box MT13)
    - Forden, Harry (Box MT13)
    - Fredlaw, Clarence (Box MT13)
    - Fredlaw, Margaret (Box MT13)
    - Gerald, Ethel (Box MT13)
    - Harris, Edna (Box MT13)
    - Harris, Elvenia (Box MT13)
    - Harris, Jeanne (Box MT13)
    - Hassell, Lula (Box MT13)
    - Haynes, Edward (Box MT13)
    - Henry, Charlie (Box MT13)
    - Johnson, Ezell (Box MT13)
    - Jones, Alexander (Box MT13)
    - Kirby, Dorothy (Box MT13)
    - Logan, Eugene (Box MT13)
    - Logan, Willie (Box MT13)
    - MacRae, George (Box MT13)
    - Mallette, John (Box MT13)
    - Mallette, Renée (Box MT13)
    - McCrae, Aaron (Box MT13)
    - McCrimmon, Marvis (Box MT13)
    - Morris, Willie (Box MT13)
    - Neal, Margaret (Box MT14)
    - Nixon, Cornelius (Box MT14)
    - O'Dell, Beryl (Box MT14)
    - Rogers, Margaret (Box MT14)
    - Saulter, Elizabeth (Box MT14)
    - Session, Audrey (Box MT14)
    - Smith, Lillian (Box MT14)
    - Smith, Rebecca (Box MT14)
    - Spaulding, John (Box MT14)
    - Spencer, Leonard (Box MT14)
    - Swain, Ernest (Box MT14)
    - Tate, Katherine (Box MT14)
    - Thomas, Esther (Box MT14)
    - Thomas, Roderick (Box MT14)
    - Todd, Bertha (Box MT14)
    - Todd, Edward (Box MT14)
    - Upperman, Leroy (Box MT14)
    - Wade, Alene (Box MT14)
    - Wade, David (Box MT14)
    - Wade, Mamie (Box MT14)
    - White, Margaret (Box MT14)
    - Williams, Lucille (Box MT14)
    - Williston Sr. High (Box MT14)
    - Wilson, Lloyd (Box MT14)
    - Woods, Dorothy (Box MT14)
- Use Tapes Series (UT), 1993-1997 [RESTRICTED], 14 boxes
  The Use Tapes Series, 1993-1997, contains a full set of the 1260 interviews conducted as part of the Behind the Veil oral history project.
  The interview tapes in this series are organized alphabetically by site, with administrative tapes at the beginning of the series, and alphabetically by surname within.
  Forty-two of these interviews are closed to all researchers; these tapes are housed separately at the end of the series. All the remaining tapes are available to researchers; however, some restrictions, such as stipulations regarding publication and profit, anonymity or transliteration of language, may apply to the use of individual interviews. Information about particular restrictions on use can be found with the printed materials in this collection. Researchers with further questions about these restrictions should consult with library staff.
  - Administration (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Crumpton, William (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Ferguson, Karen (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Mawhood, Rhonda (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Miles, Kara (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Ramsey, Sonya (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Stewart, Chris (Box UT1 Tray A)
  - Albany, Ga. and Environs
    - Billingsley, Luke (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Blount, Laura (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Bradford, Martha (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Caldwell, Leola (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Carter, Viola (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Chatmon, Thomas (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Clouden, Theressa (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Conway, Alice (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Crumbley, David (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Cuffie, Jimmie (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Cuffie, Roosevelt (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Flowers, Aurie (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Gamble, Edward, Sr. (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - George, Doris (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - George, Melvin (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Geter, Mary (Box UT1 Tray A)
    - Goines, Rebecca (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Grant, Cornelius (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Hall, James (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Hamilton, Odessa (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Harris, McCree (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Hawkins, Eva (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Hill, Arefellow (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Hudson, Irene (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Jackson, Willie (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Jenkins, Mary (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Jones, Marva (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - King, Carolyn (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - McCorico, Frances (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Miller, Josie (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Mott, James (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Nelson, Mae (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Nelson, Mamie (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Newsome, Daisy (Box UT1 Tray B)
    - Pitts, Anna (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Rogers, Olive (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Searles, Arthur (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Sherrod, Charles (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Sherrod, Shirley (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Shipp, Mary (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Spivey, Emma (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Stewart, Ada (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Taylor, John (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Taylor, Robella (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Watkins, Jurl (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Wells, Samuel (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Williams, Curtis (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Williams, Leola (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Willis, Mary (Box UT1 Tray C)
  - Arkansas
    - Alexander, Rufus (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Baker, Sherman, Sr. (Box UT1 Tray C)
    - Baltimore, Lucinda (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Black, Charles (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Briscoe, Mary (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Buffington, J. (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Caldwell, Ernest (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Chandler, Mattie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Chappel, Johnana (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Chism, Tolbert (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Clay, Florence (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Clayton, Rucker (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Clemons, Ella (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Counts, Rosetta (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Davidson, et. al., Geraldine (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Davidson, Geraldine (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Dennis, Dora (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Dilworth, Sammie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Dread, Acie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Farr, Earl (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Floyd, Annie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Ford, Georgia (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Gaylord, Ellihue, Sr. (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Giles, Malvie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Glover, Chairty (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Green, Della (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Gunthrope, Myrtle (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Hardison, Morestine (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Harris, Lotus (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Hatch, Mattie (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Hendricks, Oda (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Hollister, Major (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Howard, Helen (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Jeffers, Cleo (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Jones, Julice (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Jones, Le (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Jones, Robert (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Kimbell, George (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - Kimbell, John (Box UT1 Tray D)
    - King, Calvin, Sr. (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Kirby, Anne (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Kirby, Money (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Locke, Harrison (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Locke, Martha (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Lowe, Mattie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Lucas, Almae (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Lucas, Willie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Mallory, Kathleen (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Malone, William (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Marshall, Ulysses (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Mathis, Parie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - McDaniel, Deborah (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - McKinney, Mildred (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - McNeal, Ulysses (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Mitchell, Cleaster (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Nash, Thelma (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Pearson, Thereasa (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Pickens, Ruby (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Scott, Sam (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Sharp, Robert (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Shepherd, Carrie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Shepherd, Madge (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Story, James (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Swanigan, Daniel (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Swanigan, Katie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Thompson, Elmer (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Thompson-Marks, Lois (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Tims, Willie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Todd, Joe (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Trailor, Christine (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Turnage, Curtis (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Turnage, Elizabeth (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Tyler, Huston (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Vaughn, Thomas (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Walker, Minnie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Walker, Mollie (Box UT2 Tray A)
    - Wells, Tommy (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - White, Samella (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Wilhite, Iola (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Williams, Joe (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Williams, Johnnie (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Williams, Martin (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Williams, Oliver (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Williams, Sarah (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Wilson, Rosetta (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Woods, Delores (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Wright, Ethel (Box UT2 Tray B)
  - Birmingham, Ala. and Environs
    - Alexander, Leon (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Allen, Betty (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Anderson, Henry (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Anderson, Olivia (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Archie, Johnnie (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Battle, William (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Brown, Allie (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Brown, Earl (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Brown, George (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Cannon, James (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Cannon, Rebeca (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Caswell, Melvin (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Clarke, Juanita (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Daniel, Mollie (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Davis, Blanche (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Dean, Clarence (Box UT2 Tray B)
    - Dickson, Joe (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Fincher, Lillie (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Fisher, Annie (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Fisher, John (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Foster, Charlie (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Gardner, Edward (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Goodson, Spurgeon (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Grace, Walter (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Gratton, Charles (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Hameen, Ezekiel (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Hendricks, Lola (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Hinton, Mary (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Huntley, Horace (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Johnson, Colonel (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Jones, Dorothy (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Knowles, Helen (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Langford, Lary (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Lewis, Jessie, Sr. (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Little, JoAnna (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Lowe, James (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Milton, Annie (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Mitchell, Quitman (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Monroe, Irene (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Moore, Thomas (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Nabors, Chanie (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Nelson, Rose (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Patton, William (Box UT2 Tray C)
    - Ruffin, Mary (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Rutledge, John (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Sanders, Gertrude (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Steele, Lucy (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Taylor, Lovell (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Washington, James (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Watts, Eddie (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Wheeler, Ike (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - White, Leon (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Williams, Mazie (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Williams, Roosevelt (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Wilson, Alberta (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Wilson-Davis, Florence (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Woods, Abraham (Box UT2 Tray D)
  - Charlotte, N.C. and Environs
    - Adams, Wilhelmenia (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Aldridge, Mildred (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Alexander, Almetto (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Alexander, Jenny (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Alexander, Margaret (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Alexander, Zechariah (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Anderson, Anne (Box UT2 Tray D)
    - Ballard, Sarah (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Bates, Miriam (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Bland, Irma (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Brown, Eunice (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Burke, DeGrandval (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Byers, Eddie (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Caldwell, Bernice (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Caldwell, Mattie (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Cavers, Walter (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Colston, Thelma (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Counts, Olethea (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Cousar, Dorothy (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Crosby, Kathleen (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Davis, Mildred (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Davis, Price (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Davis, Samuel (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - DeLaine, Joseph (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Donald, Morris (Box UT3 Tray A)
    - Elder, Thereasea (Box UT3 Tray A)
      (Elder materials include videotape, "The Real Estate Report: Welcome Back Greenville")
    - Ely, Vermelle (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Ferguson, Charles (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Goins, Harry (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Goins, Sudie (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Golden, Willie (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Goodwin, Florence (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Graham, Estelle (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Hagans, Zenobia (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Hart, Alice (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Hayes, Dorothy (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Heath, Henry (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Holmes, Walter (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Hunter, Annie (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Hunter, Wright (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Jones, Cedric (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Jones, Charles (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Jones, Ione (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Leak, Doretha (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Lynch, Kathleen (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Lynch, Lucille (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - McClain, Marilyn (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - McClain, Wyonella (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - McCorkle, Alene (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - McDuffie, Jean (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - McKee, Minnie (Box UT3 Tray B)
    - Miller, Bernice (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Miller, Larry (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Morris, Ruth (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Mungo, Alma (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Neal, Margaret (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Neal, Sephus (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Oxner, Nell (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Pickens, Magnolia (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Randolph, Elizabeth (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Rann, Emery (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Ray, Clyde (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Robinson, Violet (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Sammons, Lena (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Shipman, Mamie (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Shute, Amanda (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Shute, Mathew, Sr. (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Sigler, Lloyd (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Simmons, Curtina (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Spears, Alphatene (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Spears, Rufus, Sr. (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Steele, Dorothy (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Stovall, Lille (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Strong, Clyde (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Stroud, Daisy (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Stroud, Gerson (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Stroud, Wirron (Box UT3 Tray C)
    - Swift, Beatrice (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Taylor, Mildred (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Taylor, Rosita (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Thompson, Jean (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Thornton, Anita (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Twitty, Walter (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Weathers, Maxine (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - White, Allegray (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Williams, Margaret (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Williams, Tommy (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Wilson, Catherine (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Woods, Effie (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Woods, Clifton, Jr. (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Wyche, Grace (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Wyche, Thomas (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Wynn, Maria (Box UT3 Tray D)
    - Yongue, Imogene (Box UT3 Tray D)